# **Freddy Roberts**

#### CONTACT

**E-mail:** me@freddyroberts.com **Website:** www.freddyroberts.com

**Phone:** (615)-200-8245

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS: Sass, Bourbon/Neat, Bootstrap
- JAVASCRIPT: jQuery, Underscore.js, React.js, Vue.js, and able to learn Frameworks
- UX/UI: Responsive Web Design
- Versioning/Collaborating: Git, GitHub & Strong foundation with working in team environments
- Laravel: A basic understand working in Laravel
- Development Tools: CommandLine/Terminal, Bower, Npm, Gulp, Browserify, BrowserSync, Homestead

#### **ABOUT**

I am pursuing a career in web development to engage my creative side, while also solving problems in a strategic way. Music and traveling are very strong passions of mine. While playing electric guitar for Hillsong Church, I had the opportunity to visit countries like England, Greece, Finland, Norway and Denmark. For the past 5 years I lived in Europe with my wife, who is Swedish. I love exploring different cultures, having lived on three continents has helped open my mind and given me a broader perspective on life.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance Front end developer - Nashville, TN(currently)

- Hollymeyers.com A web portfolio, where I designed and developed for scratch using html, sass, jquery.
- Hinsonpoolcare.com A small business website designed & developed using react.js & sass.

#### Textbook Charlie Front end developer - Nashville, TN 2016

- All development was in Laravel.
- Working mostly with html, css(bootstrap), and vue.js.

#### The IRON YARD Front-End Engineering - Nashville, TN2015-2016

A program facilitating projects, requirements, and teaching skills to junior developers.

- 55+hours a week building web applications, using HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Project Planning, both individually & with a team
- Worked on cross-platform projects with Ruby on Rails server-side engineers.
- Final project, Drobe, a web app built with react.js using Parse as an infrastructure https://github.com/freddyroberts

#### DHL EXPRESS Courier - Stockholm, SE2011-2015

- Excellence Time Management
- Route Planning
- Self Motivation

Freddy Roberts

### Hillsong Church Maintenance/Reception - Sydney, AU 2008-2010

- Team Work
- Service Focused Visitor Interactions
- Project Planning

## **EDUCATION**

Swedish A-D 2010 — 2011

SFI- Swedish for Immigrants

Stockholm, Sweden

Ministry & Leadership 2008 — 2009

Hillsong International Leadership College

Sydney, Australia

Freddy Roberts 2